Chitrang Patel

265 Yorkland Blvd, North York, ON M2J 1S5 | +91-8511928411 chitrang200889@gmail.com | https://chitrang200889.github.io/vcard/

Objective

I will be moving to Canda by this mid-December, and will be studying two years Co-op program of Mobile Application Design and Development at Lambton college – Toronto campus. Meantime I'm looking for part time job through which I can contribute to your organization with my knowledge and experience.

Skills

- Overall IELTS band 7.5 with individual scores; Listening 9, Reading 7, Speaking 7 and Writing - 6.5
- Managed scheduling of teaming meetings, client calls
- Have proficient etiquette to handle end users
- Developed personal and professional timeline as per priorities to complete work in time.
- Collected neccesary data with call or mail to before moving further on timeline.

Employment

Sr. Android Developer(Tech Lead)

Nov 2016 - Present

BosLeo Pvt. Ltd.

Valsad, India

- Requirement analysis and project documentation
- Translated business requirements into working soultions

Sr. Android Developer(Team Lead)

Sep 2015 - Oct 2016

Dynamic Dreamz Websolutions

Surat, India

- Communicated with end users, technical team and management to collect requirements, describe software product and feature and technical designs
- Successfully managed sport's day event

Android Developer

Krtya Softwares

Jun 2013 - Aug 2015

Surat, India

- Worked with different teams
- Requirement gathering and project estimation

Education

Master of Engineering - Computer Science

2012

Indian Institute of Science

Bangalore, India

Bachelor of Engineering - Information Technology

2010

LDCE, Gujarat University

Ahmedabad, India